<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<android.support.percent.PercentRelativeLayout android:layout_height="fill_parent"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    android:background="#ffffff"
    android:layout_width="fill_parent"
    android:orientation="vertical"
    android:paddingLeft="@dimen/activity_horizontal_margin"
    android:paddingRight="@dimen/activity_horizontal_margin"
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android">


    <android.support.percent.PercentRelativeLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="0dp"
        app:layout_heightPercent="100%">
        <ScrollView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content">
            <android.support.percent.PercentRelativeLayout
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="0dp"
                app:layout_heightPercent="100%">

                <TextView
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:id="@+id/moreinfotitle"
                    android:text="This is a learning App where you can learn five different languages Android, Java, C, C++, Python. There is a Video Tutorial where you can learn these languages easily with Video Tutorials and PDF links are also available for different books which are best books for learning these languages. You can also search our Online Projects which can be done through this App only. Basic Overview for every language is also available."
                    android:textColor="#000"
                    android:textSize="18sp"
                    android:layout_marginBottom="10dp"/>

                <TextView
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
                    android:layout_below="@+id/moreinfotitle"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:id="@+id/moreinfotitle1"
                    android:text="Android"
                    android:textColor="#000"
                    android:textSize="18sp"
                    android:layout_marginBottom="10dp"/>

                <TextView
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
                    android:layout_below="@+id/moreinfotitle1"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:id="@+id/moreinfotitle2"
                    android:text="Android is a mobile operating system developed by Google, based on the Linux kernel and designed primarily for touchscreen mobile devices such as smartphones and tablets. Android's user interface is mainly based on direct manipulation, using touch gestures that loosely correspond to real-world actions, such as swiping, tapping and pinching, to manipulate on-screen objects, along with a virtual keyboard for text input. In addition to touchscreen devices, Google has further developed Android TV for televisions, Android Auto for cars, and Android Wear for wrist watches, each with a specialized user interface. Variants of Android are also used on notebooks, game consoles, digital cameras, and other electronics.

Initially developed by Android Inc., which Google bought in 2005, Android was unveiled in 2007, along with the founding of the Open Handset Alliance – a consortium of hardware, software, and telecommunication companies devoted to advancing open standards for mobile devices. Beginning with the first commercial Android device in September 2008, the operating system has gone through multiple major releases, with the current version being 7.0 Nougat, released in August 2016. Android applications (apps) can be downloaded from the Google Play store, which features over 2.7 million apps as of February 2017. Android has been the best-selling OS on tablets since 2013, and runs on the vast majority[a] of smartphones. As of May 2017, Android has two billion monthly active users, and it has the largest installed base of any operating system.

Android's source code is released by Google under an open source license, although most Android devices ultimately ship with a combination of free and open source and proprietary software, including proprietary software required for accessing Google services. Android is popular with technology companies that require a ready-made, low-cost and customizable operating system for high-tech devices. Its open nature has encouraged a large community of developers and enthusiasts to use the open-source code as a foundation for community-driven projects, which deliver updates to older devices, add new features for advanced users or bring Android to devices originally shipped with other operating systems. The extensive variation of hardware in Android devices causes significant delays for software upgrades, with new versions of the operating system and security patches typically taking months before reaching consumers, or sometimes not at all. The success of Android has made it a target for patent and copyright litigation between technology companies."

                    android:textSize="15sp"
                    android:layout_marginBottom="10dp"/>

                <TextView
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
                    android:layout_below="@+id/moreinfotitle2"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:id="@+id/moreinfotitle3"
                    android:text="JAVA"
                    android:textColor="#000"
                    android:textSize="18sp"
                    android:layout_marginBottom="10dp"/>
                <TextView
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
                    android:layout_below="@+id/moreinfotitle3"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:id="@+id/moreinfotitle4"
                    android:text="Java is a general-purpose computer programming language that is concurrent, class-based, object-oriented,[14] and specifically designed to have as few implementation dependencies as possible. It is intended to let application developers write once, run anywhere (WORA),[15] meaning that compiled Java code can run on all platforms that support Java without the need for recompilation.[16] Java applications are typically compiled to bytecode that can run on any Java virtual machine (JVM) regardless of computer architecture. As of 2016, Java is one of the most popular programming languages in use,[17][18][19][20] particularly for client-server web applications, with a reported 9 million developers.[21] Java was originally developed by James Gosling at Sun Microsystems (which has since been acquired by Oracle Corporation) and released in 1995 as a core component of Sun Microsystems' Java platform. The language derives much of its syntax from C and C++, but it has fewer low-level facilities than either of them.

                The original and reference implementation Java compilers, virtual machines, and class libraries were originally released by Sun under proprietary licenses. As of May 2007, in compliance with the specifications of the Java Community Process, Sun relicensed most of its Java technologies under the GNU General Public License. Others have also developed alternative implementations of these Sun technologies, such as the GNU Compiler for Java (bytecode compiler), GNU Classpath (standard libraries), and IcedTea-Web (browser plugin for applets).

                The latest version is Java 8 which is the only version currently supported for free by Oracle, although earlier versions are supported both by Oracle and other companies on a commercial basis."

                android:textSize="15sp"
                android:layout_marginBottom="10dp"/>
                <TextView
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
                    android:layout_below="@+id/moreinfotitle4"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:id="@+id/moreinfotitle5"
                    android:text="PYTHON"
                    android:textColor="#000"
                    android:textSize="18sp"
                    android:layout_marginBottom="10dp"/>
                <TextView
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
                    android:layout_below="@+id/moreinfotitle5"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:id="@+id/moreinfotitle6"
                    android:text="Python is a widely used high-level programming language for general-purpose programming, created by Guido van Rossum and first released in 1991. An interpreted language, Python has a design philosophy which emphasizes code readability (notably using whitespace indentation to delimit code blocks rather than curly brackets or keywords), and a syntax which allows programmers to express concepts in fewer lines of code than might be used in languages such as C++ or Java.[22][23] The language provides constructs intended to enable writing clear programs on both a small and large scale.[24]

Python features a dynamic type system and automatic memory management and supports multiple programming paradigms, including object-oriented, imperative, functional programming, and procedural styles. It has a large and comprehensive standard library.[25]

Python interpreters are available for many operating systems, allowing Python code to run on a wide variety of systems. CPython, the reference implementation of Python, is open source software[26] and has a community-based development model, as do nearly all of its variant implementations. CPython is managed by the non-profit Python Software Foundation."

                    android:textSize="15sp"
                    android:layout_marginBottom="10dp"/>
                <TextView
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
                    android:layout_below="@+id/moreinfotitle6"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:id="@+id/moreinfotitle7"
                    android:text="C"
                    android:textColor="#000"
                    android:textSize="18sp"
                    android:layout_marginBottom="10dp"/>
                <TextView
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
                    android:layout_below="@+id/moreinfotitle7"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:id="@+id/moreinfotitle8"
                    android:text="C (/ˈsiː/, as in the letter c) is a general-purpose, imperative computer programming language, supporting structured programming, lexical variable scope and recursion, while a static type system prevents many unintended operations. By design, C provides constructs that map efficiently to typical machine instructions, and therefore it has found lasting use in applications that had formerly been coded in assembly language, including operating systems, as well as various application software for computers ranging from supercomputers to embedded systems.

C was originally developed by Dennis Ritchie between 1969 and 1973 at Bell Labs,[5] and used to re-implement the Unix operating system.[6] It has since become one of the most widely used programming languages of all time,[7][8] with C compilers from various vendors available for the majority of existing computer architectures and operating systems. C has been standardized by the American National Standards Institute (ANSI) since 1989 (see ANSI C) and subsequently by the International Organization for Standardization (ISO)."
                    android:textSize="15sp"
                    android:layout_marginBottom="10dp"/>
                <TextView
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
                    android:layout_below="@+id/moreinfotitle8"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:id="@+id/moreinfotitle9"
                    android:text="C++"
                    android:textColor="#000"
                    android:textSize="18sp"
                    android:layout_marginBottom="10dp"/>
                <TextView
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
                    android:layout_below="@+id/moreinfotitle9"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:id="@+id/moreinfotitle10"
                    android:text="C++ (pronounced cee plus plus /ˈsiː plʌs plʌs/) is a general-purpose programming language. It has imperative, object-oriented and generic programming features, while also providing facilities for low-level memory manipulation.

It was designed with a bias toward system programming and embedded, resource-constrained and large systems, with performance, efficiency and flexibility of use as its design highlights.[5] C++ has also been found useful in many other contexts, with key strengths being software infrastructure and resource-constrained applications,[5] including desktop applications, servers (e.g. e-commerce, web search or SQL servers), and performance-critical applications (e.g. telephone switches or space probes).[6] C++ is a compiled language, with implementations of it available on many platforms. Many vendors provide C++ compilers, including the Free Software Foundation, Microsoft, Intel, and IBM.

C++ is standardized by the International Organization for Standardization (ISO), with the latest standard version ratified and published by ISO in December 2014 as ISO/IEC 14882:2014 (informally known as C++14).[7] The C++ programming language was initially standardized in 1998 as ISO/IEC 14882:1998, which was then amended by the C++03, ISO/IEC 14882:2003, standard. The current C++14 standard supersedes these and C++11, with new features and an enlarged standard library. Before the initial standardization in 1998, C++ was developed by Bjarne Stroustrup at Bell Labs since 1979, as an extension of the C language as he wanted an efficient and flexible language similar to C, which also provided high-level features for program organization. The C++17 standard is due in July 2017, with the draft largely implemented by some compilers already, and C++20 is the next planned standard thereafter.

Many other programming languages have been influenced by C++, including C#, D, Java, and newer versions of C."

                    android:textSize="15sp"
                    android:layout_marginBottom="10dp"/>


            </android.support.percent.PercentRelativeLayout>
        </ScrollView>
    </android.support.percent.PercentRelativeLayout>


</android.support.percent.PercentRelativeLayout>
